Lets say we have a biased coin and
假如我们有一个偏倚硬币
it has a probability three-quarters of coming up heads, which I'll call p.
它翻出正面的概率是四分之三 我称之为 p
This coin could actually be a visitor to a webpage,
这个硬币实际上可以代表
who has a three-quarters probability of clicking a button, but
有四分之三的概率点击按钮的网页访客
I'm going to do this example with coins for simplicity.
但这里 为方便起见 我会用硬币作为示例
We we'll define success to be heads and failure to be tails.
我们将成功认作是正面 而失败是背面
This doesn't necessarily mean we're upset if we get a tails,
这并不是说如果翻出背面我们要不开心
it's just the way of specifying what the two outcomes are.
这只是为了指定两个不同结果而已
Now, let's say we flip the coin ten times.
现在 比如说我们翻十次硬币
How many times will it come up heads?
那会出现多少次正面？
Of course, it could come up heads zero times, ten times, or
当然 有可能是零次 十次
anything in between, but some outcomes will be more likely than others.
或者之间的任何数字 但是有一些结果出现的可能性会比其他更高
If we mark the probability of each number of heads,
如果我们标出出现的正面次数的概率
we'll get something that looks like this.
我们会得到类似这样的结果
As you can see, the most likely results are seven or eight heads, but
如你所见 最可能出现的结果是七次或八次正面
anything between six and nine is reasonably likely.
而六次和九次之间的任何数字也是合理的
Like Carrie mentioned, this distribution is called a binomial distribution, and
像 Carrie 提及过的 这种分布称为二项分布
we can draw it for any number of flips.
我们可以为翻任意次数的硬币绘制此图
To make it easier to do this, I'll relabel this axis
为方便起见 我将轴改为
as the percentage of flips that came up heads, or the fraction.
翻到正面的概率 或者是分数
As you increase n, the binomial distribution starts to look more and
你增加 n 的时候 二项分布会越来越像
more like a normal distribution.
正态分布
Here, you see the binomial distribution with n equals 30,
这里二项分布的 n 为 30
and the normal distribution overlaid in blue.
而正态分布用蓝色表示
The binomial and the normal distribution that approximate it
二项分布以及与其类似的正态分布
will have the same mean, which will be equal to p,
均值相同 都等于 p
the probability that the coin comes up heads.
即硬币翻出正面的概率
And the standard deviation will be the square root of p times 1 minus p over N,
标准偏差为 p 乘以 1 减 p 除以 N 的平方根
where N is the total number of flips.
N 代表翻硬币的总次数
Now in this case,
在当前情况下
we assumed that we knew the probability that the coin would come up heads.
我们之前假设我们已经知道硬币翻出正面的概率
Let's instead consider a case where we don't know that.
现在让我们来考虑下 如果我们不知道这个概率
We flip the coin 20 times, so N equals 20,
我们翻了 20 次硬币 所以 N 等于 20
and it comes up heads 16 times, which I'll call X.
其中十六次翻出正面 称为 X
Now, let's say we want to estimate the probability the coin will come up heads.
现在 加入我们想估计硬币翻出正面的概率
That is, we want to guess the bias of the coin.
也就是 我们想要猜测硬币的偏倚
Of course, this could be a fair coin that happens to come up heads more than
当然 这也可能就是一个公平硬币 刚好翻出正面多过背面
tails, but the results we saw will be more likely if the coin is biased.
但根据结果来看 硬币很可能是偏倚性的
To estimate the bias, which I'll call p hat,
要估计这个偏倚性 我称之为 p?
it's an estimate of the probability.
它是指概率的预计值
We'll take the number of heads, in this case 16,
这里 我们用出现正面的次数 这里是 16
and divide by the number of flips, in this case, 20.
除以翻硬币的次数 这里是 20
And we get four-fifths.
我们得到结果五分之四
So, our best estimate is that this coin has a probability four-fifths
所以 我们的最佳估计是该硬币翻出正面的概率
of coming up heads.
是五分之四
If you'd like to see more details on what the binomial distribution
如果你想更具体地了解不同参数的
looks like for
二项分布会是什么样的
different parameters, the page linked in the instructor's notes may be helpful.
讲师注释中的页面链接可能会有所帮助
In order to use the binomial distribution,
在使用二项分布时
a few assumptions have to hold.
必须使用一些假设
First, there have to be exactly two types of outcomes.
首先 必须有两个不同的结果
We've been calling these success and failure.
我们称之为成功与失败
And second, the events have to be independent.
第二 事件必须是独立的
Learning the outcome of one coin flip doesn't tell you anything about whether
知道了某一次翻硬币的结果
the next coin came up heads.
你也不会知道下一次翻硬币结果是什么
And finally, the events need to follow an identical distribution.
最后 事件要遵循同一种分布
That is, the probability of success needs to be the same for all of them.
也就是说 每一次翻硬币的成功概率必须是一致的
In practice,
在实践中
identifying cases where your events are independent can be kind of tricky.
要确认事件是否是独立的 有时候可能比较棘手
So let's go over some examples.
所以让我们来看看一些例子
First, suppose you shuffle a deck of 52 cards and you draw and
首先 假设你洗好一副牌 一副牌有 52 张牌
hold the first 20 cards.
然后你将前 20 张牌拿在手里
Each card is an event and the outcome is whether the card is red or black.
每张牌是一个事件 而结果是这张牌是红色还是黑色的
Next, suppose you roll a die 50 times.
然后 假设你摇骰子摇 50 次
Each roll is an event and
每摇动一次就是一个事件
you choose to label six as a success and any other result as a failure.
然后得到六为成功 其他的为失败
Next, suppose a search engine, such as Google,
然后 假设一个搜索引擎 例如 Google
is measuring how often people click on search results after making a search.
在测量大家在搜索之后点击搜索结果的频率
Each event is one search made on the search engine and
事件是在搜索引擎上进行的一次搜索
the outcome is whether the person clicked any link in the results.
而结果是这个人是否点击了结果中的任何链接
Next, supposed an online education company, like Udacity, is measuring how
然后 假设一个在线教育公司 例如优达学城 在测量
many of the students who enroll in a course complete it within two months.
加入课程的学员中 有多少在两个月内完成了课程
Each event is one student and
一个学生是一个事件
the outcome is whether the student has completed the course two months later.
结果是学生是否在两个月后完成课程
Finally, suppose an online shopping company, such as Amazon,
最后 假设一个在线购物公司例如亚马逊
is measuring how often items that are added to a shopping cart are purchased
测试一周内 用户会有多少次
within a week.
购买购物车中的物品
Each event is a single item and
每个物品是一个事件
the outcome is whether the item has been purchased a week later.
结果是是否在一周内购买了物品
For each of these situations,
针对以上情况
check the box if you think it is valid to assume a binomial distribution, and
勾选你认为能出现二项分布
specifically, think about whether the events will be independent.
具体点说 你认为事件为独立事件的选项
Some of them are a bit subjective, but take your best guess.
有一些比较主观 但尽量一试吧